priceplunge.com 2014-02-10

# Privacy Policy

**Priceplunge.com** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: priceplunge.com.

This site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and to deliver content specific to your interests.

This site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (e.g. their name and email address). priceplunge.com uses customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our Company. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor or user when necessary.

In order to best serve our customers, we may send updates that contain important information about priceplunge.com's products and services. We may also communicate with a customer to provide requested services and for account-related issues via e-mail. All emails including but not limited to promotional emails will only be sent by priceplunge.com. We do not sell subscriber e-mail addresses nor are they used by third-parties to send emails to our subscribers. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

This site contains links to other sites. priceplunge.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

## Choice/Opt-Out

This site gives users the option to remove their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  * Click here to unsubscribe or change your email options

## Personal Information Privacy

The information gathered by priceplunge.com during the order process is for the purposes of processing orders and providing updates on the status of your order. priceplunge.com will disclose your personal information to third parties to charge your credit card, process your order, ship your order, offer customer service and provide you with a credit. An example of Companies that may receive your information are: your card-issuing bank must be given your personal credit card information for payment confirmation. priceplunge.com must also disclose to parcel delivery services your address and telephone information in order to ship and deliver the items that you ordered.

priceplunge.com does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.

priceplunge.com may be required by judicial authorities or other law enforcement agencies to provide personal information. priceplunge.com will disclose personal information upon receipt of a subpoena, court order or in cooperation with a law enforcement investigation. Law enforcement agencies will have the full cooperation of priceplunge.com in identifying individuals or groups who use the services of priceplunge.com for illegal activities. priceplunge.com also reserves the right to report any activities that we may believe to be unlawful to law enforcement agencies.

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:

www.priceplunge.com  
**Priceplunge.com**  
280 Opportunity Way  
LaGrange, Ohio 44050  
United States  

If you have a question, please feel free to contact us by clicking here
